clickandc.com 2011-04-07

# None

This is the web site & online business of **Raven Squared**.  

Our postal address is   
**150 Timberline Drive  
Forsyth, MO 65653**

We can be reached via e-mail at [ sharlene@theravenproject.com](mailto:sharlene@theravenproject.com)  
our help desk located at [ http://www.RavenResponds.com](http://www.ravenresponds.com/)   
or you can reach us by telephone at 417-243-0008  

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address) and any other information voluntarily supplied by the consumer/visitor.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes and .

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by visiting us at [ http://www.RavenResponds.com](http://www.ravenresponds.com/) or clicking the unsubscribe link in any of our communications.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line or information they requested.

Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations 

With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by visiting us at [http://www.RavenResponds.com](http://www.ravenresponds.com/). 

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them.

Consumers can access this information by visiting us at [http://www.RavenResponds.com](http://www.ravenresponds.com/). 

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information.

Consumers can have this information corrected by visiting us at [http://www.RavenResponds.com](http://www.ravenresponds.com/). 

With respect to security: and When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server..

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact or us at [http://www.RavenResponds.com](http://www.ravenresponds.com/)  and let us know what part of this policy we have violated so that we may correct it immediately..

Other Privacy States That May Apply:

**1\. Our Commitment to Privacy.**  This notice describes our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy is designed to advise you about how we collect, use, and protect the Personally Identifiable Information you provide. By visiting this site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**2\. What Information is Collected.**

(a) Information You Provide to Us: 

We collect the Personally Identifiable Information you choose to enter on various pages of our site, or that you may choose to give us in some other way (such as by email, physical mail, or by telephone). For example, you will be asked to provide Personally Identifiable Information when you register for access to certain portions of our site, sign up for newsletters or mailings, or make a purchase. 

The categories of Personally Identifiable Information we collect are your first and last name, e-mail address, physical address, and telephone number.

You can choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of our services and features.

(b) Automatic Information: 

When you visit a website, you disclose certain information, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time of your visit. This site, like many other sites, records this basic information about visits to our site.

(c) “Cookies”: 

Cookies are pieces of information that are transferred to your computer from a web server. 

We use cookies to store visitor preferences, record session information (such as items that you add to your shopping cart) record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, and to customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or you can change your settings to refuse to accept cookies.

**3\. How and When the Information is Used.**  The information we collect is used for administering our business activities as follows:

            (a) to improve the content of our site;

(b) to customize the content and/or layout of site pages for each individual visitor;

(c) used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site;

(d) shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes;

(e) used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes.

**4\. How We Protect Your Information.**  The privacy and protection of your information is important to us. We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Your access to some services and content is password protected. We advise that you do not disclose your password to anyone. In addition, we recommend you sign out of password-protected services at the end of your session.  You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and this policy.

**5\. Who Has Access to the Information.**  Information about our users is important to us. Access to your information may be provided to third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site. In addition, we may sell our business or buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be transferred along with other assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order and we may disclose your information when we believe we are required to do so by law. We may disclose your information in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us and to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure.

**6\. Methods We Use to Protect Your Information.**  We use security software to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. In addition, our business practices are reviewed periodically for compliance with policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information. Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons.

**7\. Children.**  This website does not provide services or sell products to children under the age of 18\.  If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 18 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe we have received any information from or about anyone under the age of 18, please contact us at the address listed below.

**8\. How You Can Access Your Information.**  You can request access to all your personally identifiable information maintained by us by sending an e-mail to us at the address listed below. Upon request we offer you the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in your personally identifiable information. You can have this information corrected by sending us an e-mail at the address listed below.

**9\. Consent.**  By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**10\. Changes to Privacy Policy.**  If our Privacy Policy or procedures change, we will immediately post those changes to our website. Any such changes will be effective immediately upon being posted, unless otherwise stated in the change.

**11\. Effective Date.**  This Privacy Policy is effective as of 2005.

**12\. Contact E-Mail.**  You may contact us concerning this Privacy Policy at the following e-mail address  [sharlene@theravenproject.com](mailto:sharlene@theravenproject.com)
